Inventory of the Norman Allderdice Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Series II (Box 49)
  - World Anti-Communist League--Pamphlets
    - "The Chinese Communist ...," Lien, Li, 1977 (Folder 132: 19)
    - "Where the World Should Go?" Cheng-chung, Li, 1977 (Folder 132: 20)
    - "The New Strategic Situation ...," Yu-ching, Chen, 1980 (Folder 132: 21)
    - "The Relations of American Youth ...," Shih-pu, Lo, 1972 (Folder 132: 22)
    - "Mao's Purge of Senior Military Cadre,", 1972 (Folder 132: 23)
    - "Chinese Communist Criminal Acts in Persecution of Religions," Ping-wen, Shen, 1978 (Box-folder 133: 1)
    - "List of Workers under Chinese Communist Persecution," Ping, Shih, 1973 (Folder 133: 2)
    - "A Summing-Up of Chinese ...,", 1977 (Folder 133: 3)
    - "True Facts of Chinese ...,", 1974 (Folder 133: 4)
    - "True Facts of Maoist Tyranny,", 1971 (Folder 133: 5)
    - "Chinese Communists' Support ...," Ching-Lang, Tsai, 1973 (Folder 133: 6)
    - "Peking's International Propaganda Activities...," Chin, Tsai, 1975 (Folder 133: 7)
    - "Bitter Lessons from Diplomatic Relations with the Maoists," Parts I and II, Chia-pi, Tung, 1972 (Folder 133: 8)
    - "Chinese Communist Exploitation and Persecution of Intellectuals" and "Higher Education of China Mainland since Cultural Revolution," Hsueh-wen, Wang, 1976-1980 (Folder 133: 9)
    - "Changes in Relations between ...," Chien-hsun, Wang, and "Intellectual Youths on Mainland China ...," Hsiao-hsien, Wang, 1973-1980 (Folder 133: 10)
    - "About Teng Hsiao-Ping," Hsuan, Wang, 1978 (Folder 133: 11)
    - "An Analysis of ...," Sheng, Wang, 1978 (Folder 133: 12)
    - "The Foreign Trade Policy ...," O, Wei, 1978 (Folder 133: 13)
    - "Communist Theories and Tactics of Class Struggle," Chueh-yuan, Wang, 1974 (Folder 133: 14)
    - Jen-tien, Yao
      - "Peiking's Cajolery ...,", 1975 (Folder 133: 15)
      - "Transformation and ...,", 1975 (Folder 133: 16)
    - "Evolvement of Red Chinese Relations ...," Tao, Chiang, 1980 (Folder 133: 17)
    - "Communist China's ..." and "The Strategical Importance ...," Jen-tien, Yao, 1976-1977 (Folder 133: 18)
    - "Maoist New Internal ...," Hsiang-chih, Yeh, 1972 (Folder 133: 19)
    - Ching-yao, Yin (Box 134)
      - "Negotiations in an Era of Negotiation,", 1973 (Folder 134: 1)
      - "A Review of the Washington ...,", 1978 (Folder 134: 2)
      - "An Analytical Study ...,", 1978 (Folder 134: 3)
      - An Analysis of the Questions of Seeking ...,", 1977 (Folder 134: 4)
      - "Chinese Communist Foreign Policy and Trends,", 1977 (Folder 134: 5)
    - "The Guerrilla Warfare ...," Fung-tai, Young, 1973 (Folder 134: 6)
    - "Youth Problems of China," Hui, Shu, 1980 (Folder 134: 7)
    - "A Witness to Mao's Tyranny," Mao-ju, Yuan, 1972 (Folder 134: 8)
  - World Books--"Christ, Church and Communism," Leslie, Kenneth, 1962. (Folder 134: 9)
  - World Federation of Trade Union--"Free Trade Unions Remain ...,", 1949. (Folder 134: 10)
  - World Federation of Democratic Youth and the International Union of Students--"With Vietnam ...,", 1969?. (Folder 134: 11)
  - World Labor Zionist Movement
    - "The Israel-Arab Conflict ...,", undated. (Folder 134: 12)
    - "Israel between Two Imperialisms," Maerz, Eduard, undated. (Folder 134: 13)
    - "Israel and the Third World," Groman, David, 1970. (Folder 134: 14)
    - "Arab Terror," Yahalom, Yiftah, undated. (Folder 134: 15)
  - Post War World Council--"World Federation: What Are the Difficulties," Thomas, Norman, 1942. (Folder 134: 16)
  - World Law Fund--"A Comparison and Evaluation ...," McVitty, Marion H., 1964. (Folder 134: 17)
  - The World Socialist Party--The Western Socialist, 1978. (Folder 134: 18)
  - World View Publishers--Griswold (Folder 134: 19)
  - World Youth Congress--"Brother India," Patel, Rajni, undated. (Folder 134: 20)
  - Young Americans for Freedom
    - Did You Ever See a ...," edited by Buckley, William F., Jr., undated. (Folder 134: 21)
    - "Conservatism for the New Generation,", undated. (Folder 134: 22)
      Selected chapters from a book
    - "Highlights of International ...,", 1968. (Folder 134: 23)
    - "No Amnesty,", undated. (Folder 134: 24)
    - "The Fascist Threat to America," Wheeler, Richard S., undated. (Folder 134: 25)
    - "Young Americans for Freedom: First National Award,", 1961. (Folder 134: 26)
    - "Rebels with a Cause,", 1968. (Folder 134: 27)
  - Young Communist League of America
    - "We Take Our Stand,", 1937. (Folder 134: 28)
      Digest of principles and by-laws
    - "Program of ...,", undated. (Folder 134: 29)
  - Young Friends Movement (YFM)--"The Joy that Is Set before Us," Boulding, Elise, 1956. (Folder 134: 30)
  - Youth International Publishers--"Where to Begin?" Fuernberg, F., undated. (Folder 134: 31)
  - Young People's Socialist League--"Leon Sedoff: Son, Friend, Fighter," Trotsky, Leon, 1938. (Folder 134: 32)
  - Youth Publishers
    - "Young Communists ...," Green, Gil, 1935. (Folder 134: 33)
    - "Lenin, Liebknecht, Luxemburg," Steele, Al, 1934. (Folder 134: 34)
  - Ziemssen, Dietrich, "The Malmédy Trial,", 1950?. (Folder 134: 35)
  - Zionist Organization of America--"Arab Terror ...," Schechtman, Joseph B., 1969. (Folder 134: 36)
  - Miscellany, 1971-1973. (Folder 134: 37)
- Oversize Materials (Box 135)
  - Champion Papers--"The War We Are In," View 1, 1960. (Folder 135: 1)
  - World Anti-Communist League
    - "Charts Concerning Chinese Communists on the Mainland," Twenty-Sixth Series, Part I, and Thirty-Fifth Series, 1972-1978 (Folder 135: 2)
    - "Charts Concerning Chinese Communists on the Mainland," Twenty-Seventh Series, Part II, 1972 (Folder 135: 3)
  - World Committee for a World Constitutional Convention--"Preparatory Congress ...,", 1963. (Folder 135: 4)
  - Sanborn, Herbert, "The International Conspiracy,", undated. (Folder 135: 5)
    Typescript book